Man, it's freezing.
How long have we been at it today? Jeez.
I haven't eaten anything since morning. I'm starving!
What should I get for dinner?
Uh, yeah, but you said
bigger is better, remember?
You said if they're gonna fight,
heavier is better.
Okay, I'll look for one and call you back.
Huh, he's not here. Where'd he go now?
Man, what a pain. Bathroom break?
Hey, check this out!
Think it eats fish sausage?
Teehee.
Wait, wasn't that thing in the tournament?
C'mon, pandas don't eat meat. They eat bamboo.
Here you go. It's tasty-tasty fish sausage.
Take this!
I'll have the fish sausage, thank you.
No cameras on the emergency stairs!
Yo!
Panda, are you sure about this?
This could cause trouble later.
S'all good, man!
Let's secure the area near the door.
Geh! Kirara!
Why isn't Kirara with Hakari?!
Panda?
And that spiky-haired kid.
If Panda helped him sneak in here,
does that mean he's with Jujutsu Tech?!
That means Yu is with Jujutsu Tech, too!
Kin's in danger!
Boss, I need to—
Divine Dogs: Totality!
Hop!
Fushiguro?!
My Divine Dog was thrown back?!
No, judging from what Panda said,
it couldn't get close!
I've already marked Panda.
The monitoring room's up ahead!
Kirara is planning to head back to Hakari!
Wait, Kirara! We're not your enemies!
We just want to ask Hakari for a favor!
I don't believe you!
I'm disappointed in you, Panda!
Oh, you're doing that thing where I can't get close!
So Kirara can't get close to us either?
Fushiguro?!
There's more to it than that.
I can't separate from Divine Dog either!
What kind of cursed technique is this?!
Listen to me!
Hell no!
Now I've gone cold!
We're in a stalemate.
Perfect.
Kirara!
We're not exactly with Jujutsu Tech!
You know the current situation in Tokyo, don't you?
The barriers that sprung up everywhere
are all related as well.
It was an unprecedented attack
of jujutsu terrorism!
We need Hakari's help!
You're the ones who cut us out first.
You reap what you sow.
I told you, we're not with Jujutsu Tech!
What happened between you
and the higher-ups?
They fought with the conservatives.
Their idea of "conservative" goes
beyond just their policy toward regulations.
They have set ideas of what jujutsu should be.
Kugisaki's technique is a good example.
That's the kind of classic jujutsu
the conservatives like.
Remember those cursed videos that were popular a while back?
Jujutsu has been blending with technology over time.
And when it starts affecting cursed techniques,
the conservatives get fussy.
Kin's technique is a perfect example.
Those idiots up top lost because they're like that.
But you guys have Gojo Satoru
to wipe your asses.
I don't see why you need us.
So the obvious assumption is that you're lying
and are here for some other reason.
Mr. Gojo was sealed.
That's why we lost.
Oh no!
Kirara doesn't believe us!
Well, I kinda get it.
But this person is the one closest to Hakari!
Rabbit Escape!
Bunnies?
If we can convince Kirara,
negotiations with Hakari will go more smoothly!
Acrux?!
Gacrux?!
That's a lot of them. What's he up to?
My technique marks cursed energy.
It treats sorcerers and their cursed beasts
as one and the same.
At this rate, you'll keep attracting them
like that doggy earlier,
until you're crushed by your own cursed beasts.
Panda! How was Rabbit Escape?!
Almost as cute as me!
I'm asking what they could and couldn't get close to!
Oh.
They got close to me
and the second floor no problem,
but not Kirara or the monitoring room door!
Do you have a star
and a word anywhere on your body?
Huh?
Oh!
I-M-A-I?
I should have one too...
Ima? Ima? Imai?
It says Imai!
Found it!
It's Acrux, just like Rabbit Escape!
It must be on Divine Dog too.
I still don't know anything about it,
but I'll give it a shot.
I've figured it out!
This technique is based on a constellation!
That much is obvious to anyone
who knows this stuff.
The constellation it's based on is...
the Southern Cross!
Shit!
We both gave it away!
He had "No way!" written all over his face!
He wasn't sure my technique
was based on the Southern Cross!
But I gave him the same "No way!" look!
I basically confirmed it for him!
If he figures out my technique,
he'll be able to enter the monitoring room!
I have to stop him here!
Back in a stalemate again?
So it really was the Southern Cross?
I have Tsumiki to thank for that.
I don't know anything else, though.
Also, wasn't the Southern Cross
a four-star constellation?
Fushiguro!
So I can get close to Panda.
Panda, the Southern Cross has four stars, right?
Huh? Well, it is a cross.
Yeah, I guess so.
Kirara's technique marks each of us
with one of the stars in the Southern Cross.
I thought it used that
to force a certain distance between us.
But Kirara can approach the door,
and you and I can approach each other.
What if it's just Kirara's and the door's stars repelling ours?
If that were the case, Kirara would just
flee into the monitoring room.
Oh, right.
Hugging the door from the inside would leave us stuck.
Okay, how about this?
Star A can approach star B but B can't approach A.
Each star only pairs with one and can only approach that one.
Like in rock-paper-scissors.
But you and I can approach each other
and move without issue.
So that's not it, then.
I think it's like a stamp rally with a set route,
which you have to follow in order.
And anything with the same mark gets drawn together.
Makes sense.
But what if the sorcerer isn't counted as a target?
That can't be it, because Kirara
couldn't get close to Divine Dog earlier.
Right now, Kirara is keeping an eye on us
in case we clear certain conditions
and break into the monitoring room.
Then there must be at least five stars.
Right.
If my stamp rally theory is correct,
then one of us should've been able to approach
Kirara if there were only four stars.
So there has to be a fifth star we must pass through
to reach Kirara and the door.
What if there are six or seven stars?
I'd like to believe that's not the case.
Five stars in a cross is confusing enough.
If they've figured it out,
I'll go all out!
Panda!
I'm good! Don't worry about me!
Fushiguro! Find the star!
Wait! Don't throw the car!
Huh?
That car is marked with the same Imai star as you!
If you throw it, it'll just come back or pull you in
like Divine Dog did to me!
Touching the target must be required to mark it.
But Kirara hasn't touched me or Rabbit Escape.
The only contact was with Divine Dog.
Meaning Kirara is marking
cursed energy, not objects!
To mark doors and cars, someone's cursed energy
has to be infused into them ahead of time.
I knew it!
The car has someone else's cursed energy residuals!
Assuming the technique doesn't have much range,
the residuals for the other star should be...
There!
The fifth star!
I don't see any more residuals from anyone other than us.
Since Kirara's own cursed energy is already marked,
it can't be used to mark objects
with the same Acrux star that I'm marked with.
That means no launching things at me
like that car earlier!
Once I touch that, I can approach Kirara!
Fushiguro's hypothesis was correct.
Kirara's cursed technique,
Love Rendezvous,
apportions five stars to targets' cursed energy
with the Southern Cross as a base.
For one star to approach another,
it must follow a predetermined order.
And things marked with
the same star attract each other.
You're incredible.
You actually figured out my technique.
Panda!
Here we go!
The order follows the stars from nearest to farthest.
Constellations may look flat,
but they do, of course, have depth.
Each star is a different distance from the Earth.
Weren't you a little too quick to conclude
I couldn't throw things at you?
I can simply remove the Ginan star
on my own cursed energy
and mark things with the same
Acrux star that's on you!
Wha—
What?!
How?! Where did that come from?!
Oh, I get it!
That boy never dismissed his doggy cursed beast!
Did he figure out which of the
marked objects would pull the other?!
He put a wall between
himself and his cursed beast to block it.
Then unleashed the doggy
when I was in a line between them!
Love Rendezvous, release!
Please, hear us out.
Did you really set that up on purpose?
You couldn't have known if you or the doggy
would get pulled toward the other.
I took a gamble, but now I'm certain.
The one with more cursed energy output
pulls the other, right?
At first, I was pulled toward Divine Dog,
but when I reinforced my cursed energy
to defend against your attacks,
the opposite happened.
Are you really a first-year?
You aren't cute at all.
Please. We don't have time.
Please hear us out.
Fine.
Itadori?!
Fushiguro, Panda...
Stay out of this!
Underestimating me, huh?
Straight to the face!
This brat! He's not even trying to dodge!
You're nuts.
This isn't like the fight in Shibuya.
This is basically a rite of passage
to make Hakari acknowledge me.
I won't dodge. I won't fight back.
Not until he caves.
Interesting. I'll hear you out.
As long as you remain standing!
Kin!
These kids just want your help!
Hear them out!
I just said I would!
Tell me, Itadori, why me?
This is the first time we've met, yeah?
So why put your faith in me?
Because my friends all said you're strong.
Yeah, figures.
When a sorcerer asks another sorcerer for help,
they're obviously asking them to risk their lives together!
Do you have the fever
to make me put my life on the line?!
Show me! Right here and now!
Instead you're telling me you came here
because someone told you to?
What the hell's old man Yaga doing?!
He should be weeding out losers like you!
I don't have any "fever."
Huh?
I'm a cog.
Just another part of the machine sorcerers need
to keep exorcising curses—a cog.
Wait, wait, wait. Are you for real?
That's lame as hell.
This is bad!
Itadori, that's enough!
Hurts, doesn't it?
According to Gojo, my cursed energy is
coarser and grittier than others'.
You dead?
Hey, Panda! Sea Urchin Head!
Take Itadori and get lost!
Don't come ba—
Huh?!
He took three unguarded blows!
And I roughed him up before that too!
What are you made of?
I'm a cog.
Cogs have a function.
My function is to keep exorcising curses.
If I need you for that,
then I won't back down until you say yes.
Tell me, Hakari.
What is your function?
This kid...
So this is the fever of a cog?
Fine. I'll just keep punching—
Kin.
Aren't you heated up?
Fever never lies.
You guys, get down here.
Huh?
Let's cut a deal.
Huh? It's resolved?
Did you just convince him?
Yup.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We may hate the upper brass,
but Kin always burned hottest
when he was helping others at Jujutsu Tech.
Ow!
Hm?
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong,
ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong!
What?!
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong,
ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong!
A player has added a new rule to the Culling Game!
Rule 9: Players shall be able to view
the following information on other players:
name, points, number of rules added, and current colony.
You have scored five points.
'Cause I killed him. Duh.
They're all too damn weak.
It was better 400 years ago.
Where are you, Sukuna?
You have exceeded 200 points.
Would you like to spend 100 points
to add a rule to the Culling Game?
Right, the rules.
I want the players' names and their point totals
to get a sense of their strength.
Oh, but points go down when adding a rule.
So I'd need the number of rules they added, too.
And also which colony they're in.
Kogane.
Add a rule.
Reveal that info for every player.
This is the space between
dreams and reality. It's a curse.
How does he know my name?
I'm not like Itadori.
Once you step inside,
you, too, become a player!
...and make them add a rule
to let Tsumiki escape the Culling Game!